I am the man
Whoa
I can't let no more
I'm out of my body
Lose, whoa
You know that I am the man
I know one thing I can't win the plan
We've been on bus and I'm bad
Believe me, that's what I want to keep saying
I see that I barely can stand
Taking these drugs and I'm all in the train
I see this wasn't the plan
Whoa
You know that I am the man
I know one thing I can't win the plan
We've been on bus and I'm bad
Believe me, that's what I want to keep saying
I see that I barely can stand
Taking these drugs and I'm all in the train
I see this wasn't the plan
I see what I want and you do it to me
I become like the knees bend
Can't ain't right up here that's right on my hand
Made double gaze on on my man
While there were a b***h on my head
Couping up a butter but I can't get fed
Stay with your b***h and I'm talking a plan
Make a leg walk like doors on the land
Yeah
Where am I?
I'm so out of my body
I'm so out of my
I'm out of my body
What the plan?
What the b***h?
Don't let them play
I'm out of my body
I'm so out of my body
Yeah
B.C. Boy
Yellow Diamond T.C. Boy
I be rocking wiki boy
Nick Tibwe's that easy boy
She said can you kiss me boy?
I am B.C. Boy
It's talking to him
I just been boy
I'm N.G. I've been on board
Same rights in my bank account
It's the same as...