I am the man
Whoa
I can't let no more
I'm out of my body
Lose, whoa
You know that I am the man
I know one thing I can't win the plan
We've been on bus and I'm bad
Believe me, that's what I want to keep saying
I see that I barely can stand
Taking these drugs and I'm all in the train
I see this wasn't the plan
Whoa
You know that I am the man
I know one thing I can't win the plan
We've been on bus and I'm bad
Believe me, that's what I want to keep saying
I see that I barely can stand
Taking these drugs and I'm all in the train
I see this wasn't the plan
I see what I want and you do it to me
I become like the knees bend
Can't ain't right up here that's right on my hand
Made double gaze on on my man
While there were a b***h on my head
Couping up a butter but I can't get fed
Stay with your b***h and I'm talking a plan
Make a leg walk like doors on the land
Yeah
Where am I?
I'm so out of my body
I'm so out of my
What the plan
I'm talking about
What the fuck
Don't make no sense
I'm talking about
What the fuck
Yeah, busy boy
Yellow diamond busy boy
I be rocking wiki boy
Mix it with that busy boy
She said can you kiss me boy
I am a bitch I'm too annoyed
I am a bitch who won the court
It's talking to him I just been poor
I'm a nigga I've been on board
Same rights and my bank account is the same as